What are things, if any, that you've
trained yourself to categorically say no
to or be wary of in service of
simplicity? Do you have certain rules
for yourself?
>> I really do sacrifice efficiency for
meaning pretty often. Reading The 4-Hour
Workweek was transformative for me and
it really put a fire underneath me to
find a way to come up with protocols to
live my days by and everything like
that. And I've done so many different
productivity type efficiency things over
the years. In the last few years, I'll
find myself burning out if I separate
myself from the task. If I do things for
efficiency, personally, and I also
realize who I'm talking to here. I have
so much respect for what you guys do and
how you can be peak performers and all
that stuff. It's just for me personally,
I struggle with it. I struggle when I'm
giving myself, "Okay, the next 4 hours
and then I'm going to meditate with Baby
Yoda on top of a mountain."
>> Have you been watching my nanny cam?
>> I will sacrifice efficiency for meaning
a lot of times. And it doesn't make me
the most productive, but the way I
justify it to myself is like it's a long
play. I want to still be doing this for
my family in 20 years. I want to still
be writing and loving what I'm doing.
So, if I'm writing and I'm not feeling
it or I'm researching and I'm just not
in it, then I will go and hang out with
my family or I'll go and do something
else. Talk to my friend Dave.